Recep Ahmet Saritekin

Mugla Sitki Kocman University Engineering Department Kotekli/Mugla

🛘 (+90) 537-247-9500 | 💌 rahmetsaritekin@gmail.com | 🖸 us | 🤡 saritekin | 📓 syny | 🛅 rahmetsaritekin | 💌 distortionalist

"We lay on our backs, looking at the ceiling and wondering what God had wrought when He made life so sad. Jack Kerouac-On The Road"

Summary_

During my high school life I became an semi-expert in the Wing-Tsun that is a traditional Southern Chinese Kung-fu styles and I still use philosophy of Wing-Tsun in my life. I have played guitar and had a sing on my own and with many different music groups since high school. I have great interest in literature, philosophy, physics, mathematics and art. In general, I read, write, research and discuss. I'm traveling to Turkey, which is also the first goal with hitchhiking. I can stay on the road for a long time. My goal is not to arrive somewhere, I like the road itself, the blessings that the road offers me.

Currently, I am a third grade computer engineering student at Muğla Sıtkı Koçman University. I am someone who likes to solve problems in new ways and learn new technologies when needed. I've been learning new things by learning to learn for 3 years. I adopt free software philosophy and I like to contribute to open source projects in Github(tensorflow, jax, fastai, dffml, etc). Previously, I was working as a full-stack developer and a blockchain developer. The last summer I worked on TensorFlow with Google Brain Team on Google Summer of Code. Now I'm doing research on machine learning and deep learning of math. In my work environment, I use Vim, jetbrains IDE's, jupyter notebook, linux and OSX.

Work Experience __

Koc University AI Lab

Istanbul, Turkey June 2020, Aug. 2020

INTERN

• I learned Julia language, Knet.jl and ONNX.

- My project was about Knet.jl that is a popular deep learning framework written by Koc University.
- I worked for implementation of ONNX to Knet.jl
- · Knet.jl is very low level library so when adding operators to ONNX, I added missing functions to Knet.jl like GlobalAveragePool, BatchNormalization, Cast, Transpose, etc.

Google Summer of Code <TensorFlow>

CA, United States

INTERN

May. 2019, 25 Aug. • I worked in the TensorFlow Dataset repository with Google Brain developers for 3 months.

• I added some new features, hunted bugs, reviewed pull requests, issues, etc.

Allonzi Istanbul, Turkey

CREATOR & SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Nov. 2018, May. 2019

· A social app that guides people on their journey.

Inotek Robotic AR-GE Mugla, Turkey

CREATOR & ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE RESEARCHER

Sep. 2017, PRESENT

- By collecting data from IOT devices in air, sea, air and forests, we need to determine the fire detection and so on.
- We are developing our own UAV (Unmanned Aerial Vehicle), drones and 3D printers.

Cryptouch Mugla, Turkey

CREATOR & BLOCKCHAIN ENGINEER

Nov. 2017 - Sep. 2018

- Special communication application using blockchain and IPFS in infrastructure.
- It has a distributed infrastructure focused on freedom, high security, scalability and permanency.
- Specific networks can be set up to certain people or individuals without external access.

Speakmates Tokyo, Japan

FREELANCER FULL STACK DEVELOPER & DJANGO DEVELOPER

Oct. 2017 - Jan. 2018

· A website that offers a platform where local or foreign language consultants and small groups of people who want to learn a foreign language can find each other and meet in comfortable places.

Honors & Awards

2018 Champion, Genç Beyinler Yeni Fikirler Idea Competition Izmir, Turkey 2013 5nd, Ankara Ataturk Marathon Run Ankara, Turkey 2010 Finalist, Turkey Futsal Tournament İstanbul, Turkey 2009 Champion, Table Tennis City Tournament Düzce, Turkey

JULY 28, 2020 RECEP A. SARITEKIN · RESUME **Presentation**

Women TechMakers Bolu IDW 2020

Online

Speaker <TensorFlow> May 2020

- I speak about TensorFlow Addons, Dataset, Hub, TensorBoard.
- I told a road map for Deep Learning and TensorFlow.
- I explained how to contribute to TensorFlow. What is the SIG? How can you join the community of TensorFlow and what does the communities

Google Developer Student Club

Online

SPEAKER < GSOC ON TENSORFLOW>

April 2020

- · I shared my internship experiences.
- I informed about what is GSOC, how it works, how can you apply, what should you do etc.

Developer Conference

Muğla, Turkey

SPEAKER < NEURAL NETWORKS AND DEEP LEARNING>

Nov. 2018

I speak about basics of neural networks and modern deep learning applications.

Teknopark İzmir International Blockchain Workshop

İzmir, Turkey

SPEAKER < BLOCKCHAIN BASED SECURE COMMINICATION APPLICATION PROPOSAL: CRYPTOUCH>

May. 2018

• I speak about the advantages and business areas of my own project Cryptouch.

ISDFS 2018: 6th International Symposium on Digital Forensic and Security

Antalya, Turkey

SPEAKER < BLOCKCHAIN BASED SECURE COMMINICATION APPLICATION PROPOSAL: CRYPTOUCH>

Mar. 2018

• I explained my new project Cryptouch's security infrastructure in this conference.

Developer Conference Muğla, Turkey

Speaker <'tir GIT> Feb. 2018

· I speak about GIT(the version control system) infrastructure, explained the whole documentation in this conference.

Education

MSKU (Muğla Sıtkı Koçman University Faculty of Engineering))

Muğla, Turkey

COMPUTER ENGINEERING UNDERGRADUATE EDUCATION

Sep. 2017 - Exp. Aug. 2021

I am trying to develop myself on the computer scienc by benefiting from the experiences of my teachers.

MSKU(Muğla Sıtkı Koçman University Faculty of Foreign Languages)

Muğla, Turkey

PREPARATORY EDUCATION

Sep. 2016 - Aug. 2017

I received a one-year preparatory education for 100% English Computer Engineering department.

Ankara Police Collage

Ankara, Turkey

HIGH SCHOOL Sep. 2011 - Exp. Apr. 2015

• I was educated until the third year as the last students of the College(it's a high school). Then it was closed because of political reasons.

Extracurricular Activity

Unnamed Mugla

Guitarist April. 2020 - PRESENT

• Our group consists of a synthesist working with old famous rock stars(Pentagram, Ogun Sanlisoy etc.), oboe performer in an orchestra, metal guitarist who is interest in artificial intelligence and a bass guitar player with a belly:) We make psychedelic music and usually try to improvise. We supply our electricity with solar energy and we are jamming in nature. This gives us a different inspiration. We have a really great music and I believe that the future of my band will be awesome.

Zeki ve White Streets

SOLO GUITARIST & BACK VOCAL

Jan. 2018 - PRESENT

• I am coming from metal guitar and I found a new friend who coming from classical guitar and we are create different taste improvisation musics that comes metal and classic touches and these are very absurd musics.

Dertsiz Deli ******

SOLO GUITARIST & BACK VOCAL Jan. 2017 - Dec. 2018

· Together with my vocalist friend, we try to mumbling little things and make music. We will share our musics in different social medias.

High School Rock Band Düzce, Turkey

Solo Guitarist & Back Vocal Apr. 2016 - Jun. 2016

· We gave concerts at the festivals and graduations at high schools in Düzce.

July 28, 2020 Recep A. Saritekin · Resume 2

Ankara Police College Wing Tsun Team

Ankara, Turkey Sep. 2012 - Apr.2015

COACH ASSISTANT

• I would help the teacher during training, I would check and help my friends.

PKMG (Police College Rock Band)

Ankara, Turkey

SOLO GUITARIST & BACK VOCAL

Oct. 2013 - Apr. 2015

- In the rock band of the school, I learned to be a team with my friends, to do something together and to produce new things.
- We attended the national high school music competition on behalf of our school.
- We gave small concerts in different places.

Ankara Police College Athletics Team

Ankara, Turkey

MIDDLE DISTANCE AND FLAG RUNNER

Sep. 2012 - Jun. 2013

• With our national instructor Adil and my friends, we participated in competitions and won prizes together for a year.